// Questions Data
const quizDataBase = [
    {
        question: "Q1. What is the full form of HTML?",
        a: "Hello To My Land",
        b: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        c: "Hyper Text mprocessor land",
        d: "Hyperlinks To markup language",
        ans: "ans2"
    },
    {
        question: "Q2. Who is making the Web standard?",
        a: "Mozilla",
        b: "Microsoft",
        c: "Google",
        d: "The World Wide Consortium ",
        ans: "ans4"
    },
    {
        question: "Q3. What is the full form of CSS?",
        a: "Cascading Style Sheet",
        b: "Cardova styling shape",
        c: "Crying user style",
        d: "Cascading super script",
        ans: "ans1"
    },
    {
        question: "Q4. Is Java and Javascript The Same?",
        a: "Yes",
        b: "No",
        c: "They both are the same",
        d: "There are no Java. there are javascript",
        ans: "ans2"
    },
    {
        question: "Q5. What is the full form of WWW?",
        a: "World wide web",
        b: "Wide world web",
        c: "Wrong wide word",
        d: "All of them",
        ans: "ans1"
    },
    {
        question: "Q6. Who Is The Best Developer?",
        a: "Coding Fire",
        b: "The Dev Ninja",
        c: "All Developer",
        d: "Coding With Kenny",
        ans: "ans3"
    },
    {
        question: "Q7. What Language Is Used To Create Webpages?",
        a: "C++",
        b: "C",
        c: "FTP",
        d: "HTML",
        ans: "ans4"
    },
    {
        question: "Q8. Which two tags are required for every webpage?",
        a: "<html> and <body>",
        b: "<title> and <p>",
        c: "<html> and <head>",
        d: "<h1> and <p>",
        ans: "ans1"
    },
    {
        question: "Q9. What do you need to create webpages?",
        a: "A text editor",
        b: "Special software",
        c: "Your own server",
        d: "A super fast computer",
        ans: "ans1"
    },
    {
        question: "Q10. What software needed to view webpages that you create?",
        a: "Command Promt",
        b: "Linux",
        c: "A web browser",
        d: "A compiler",
        ans: "ans3"
    }
];